[
    {
        "question": "Is Python case sensitive when dealing with identifiers?",
        "a": "no",
        "b": "yes",
        "c": "machine dependent",
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a keyword?",
        "a": "eval",
        "b": "assert",
        "c": "nonlocal",
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is an invalid statement?",
        "a": "abc = 1,000,000",
        "b": "a b c = 1000 2000 3000",
        "c": "a,b,c = 1000, 2000, 3000",
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the correct operator for power(x^y)?",
        "a": "X^y",
        "b": "X^^y",
        "c": "X**y",
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of these is floor division?",
        "a": "//",
        "b": "/",
        "c": "%",
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the output of print 0.1 + 0.2 == 0.3?",
        "a": "True",
        "b": "Error",
        "c": "False",
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these in not a core data type?",
        "a": "Lists",
        "b": "Class",
        "c": "Dictionary",
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following will run without errors?",
        "a": "round(45.8)",
        "b": "round(6352.898,2,5)",
        "c": "round()",
        "answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "In order to store values in terms of key and value we use what core data type.",
        "a": "list",
        "b": "tuple",
        "c": "dictionary",
        "answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the type of inf?",
        "a": "Float",
        "b": "Int",
        "c": "Char",
        "answer": "A"
    }
]